<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30DaysApp</string>
    <string name="day1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="day4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="day5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="day6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="day7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="day8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="day9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="day10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="day11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="day12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="day13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="day14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="day15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="day16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="day17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="day18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="day19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="day20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="day21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="day22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="day23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="day24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="day25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="day26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="day27">Day 27</string>
    <string name="day28">Day 28</string>
    <string name="day29">Day 29</string>
    <string name="day30">Day 30</string>
    <string name="quote1">Tough times don’t last. Tough people do.</string>
    <string name="quote2">It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop.</string>
    <string name="quote3">Everything you’ve ever wanted is on the other side of fear.</string>
    <string name="quote4">Pain is temporary. Quitting lasts forever.</string>
    <string name="quote5">A problem is a chance for you to do your best.</string>
    <string name="quote6">Hard times don’t create heroes. It is during the hard times when the ‘hero’ within us is revealed.</string>
    <string name="quote7">It’s not about perfect. It’s about effort.</string>
    <string name="quote8">Believe you can and you’re halfway there.</string>
    <string name="quote9">Difficult roads always lead to beautiful destinations.</string>
    <string name="quote10">Your time is limited, so don’t waste it living someone else’s life.</string>
    <string name="quote11">Perseverance is failing 19 times and succeeding the 20th.</string>
    <string name="quote12">Goals may give focus, but dreams give power.</string>
    <string name="quote13">You cannot fail at being yourself.</string>
    <string name="quote14">If you cannot do great things, do small things in a great way.</string>
    <string name="quote15">When you know what you want, and want it bad enough, you’ll find a way to get it.</string>
    <string name="quote16">I’d rather regret the things I’ve done than regret the things I haven’t done.</string>
    <string name="quote17">Motivation is what gets you started. Habit is what keeps you going.</string>
    <string name="quote18">Done is better than perfect.</string>
    <string name="quote19">I didn’t get there by wishing for it or hoping for it, but by working for it.</string>
    <string name="quote20">Don’t ask if your dream is crazy, ask if it’s crazy enough.</string>
    <string name="quote21">Success is what happens after you have survived all of your disappointments.</string>
    <string name="quote22">Aim for the moon. If you miss, you may hit a star.</string>
    <string name="quote23">Move out of your comfort zone. You can only grow if you are willing to feel awkward and uncomfortable when you try something new.</string>
    <string name="quote24">Things work out best for those who make the best of how things work out.</string>
    <string name="quote25">Start where you are. Use what you have. Do what you can.</string>
    <string name="quote26">Perseverance is the hard work you do after you get tired of doing the hard work you already did.</string>
    <string name="quote27">We may encounter many defeats but we must not be defeated.</string>
    <string name="quote28">Expect problems and eat them for breakfast.</string>
    <string name="quote29">Strength doesn’t come from what you can do. It comes from overcoming the things you once thought you couldn’t.</string>
    <string name="quote30">We don’t develop courage by being happy every day. We develop it by surviving difficult times and challenging adversity.</string>
</resources>